[music]
>> Okay.
Questions?
Just how
did Saint come out of the I know it was
a walk-through. You said you might have
a little bit more information last
night. Just how's it going so Yeah, it's
positive news, but but
you know, it's a little he's a little
irritated, you know, there's a little
irritation. So short week, you know,
we'll see.
But I would say it's still positive
news.
And obviously
playoffs are are still possibility.
I'm just curious, do you weigh at any
point just the need to maybe see some
young guys and and get them extra reps
here
just forward thinking beyond the season?
Uh
I mean I my my my thought right now is
is
going in with what we've had, you know.
Um
you know, the guys that
that we feel like um
give us a chance here
to win this game. So
for the most part it'll be status quo,
you know.
How does that relate to the center
position? Kings have played pretty well
the other day obviously and Yeah, I'm
just I was encouraged by Kingsley, you
know, I thought he did a good job. So
we're kind of weighing that right now
too and
you know, then Graham's dealt with his
knee a little bit. So
um
just thinking about it.
What do you guys have to do to
prove against the the blitz that gave
you some trouble last time?
Yeah, I mean there
man, it takes all of us, you know,
certainly, you know, that one of the big
things is third down today is
putting in a plan that that allows us to
handle some of this, you know, there's
there's going to be a ton put on golf,
you know, that's
um he's going to have a lot on his plate
and
you know, he always has a lot on his
plate. I mean nothing's new there, but
you know, these guys present a lot of
problems, a lot of challenges. So it
starts there and then we got to play
fast, man. We got to play fast. We got
to make sure communication is everybody
is doing the same thing. We're honoring
the
what golf says, we're honoring what
Kingsley says or Graham depending on who
plays um
and make sure we go.
Uh
and and then
you get the ball in your hands, you get
you got to find a way to get it to the
first and if it's not it's close enough
for us to
um to go another down possibly. Coach,
we saw your guys get named to the Pro
Bowl today. One guy is Jack Campbell in
particular. Can you speak about him as
he's in it and him [snorts] you know,
entering that that mix as well with
those guys? Yeah, just he's
you know,
I'm happy in that regard for all those
guys, you know.
Um
but he's he's gotten better every year.
You know, he's been on this upward
trajectory. He's just continued to
improve.
God doesn't say a lot. He just works,
you know, he's just a workhorse and uh
he's all about ball. He loves ball and
uh
you know, he he does it for the guy next
to him. So just
his production speaks for itself. He's
come so far
and you know, there again, I mean he's
he's taken more reps than anybody we've
got on this team to this point which is
a ton.
You know, that's a lot and
so
anyway, you know, proud of him. And
Kevin just made the announcement over in
Minnesota that's going to be Bryce
Perkins at quarterback on on Thursday.
Just what you've seen from him in the in
the limited times he's he's stepped in
and played. Well, if you give him time
to see it, he can throw it and he's got
receivers to throw to.
I know that. The guy's accurate and
you know, so I I think it it really
falls in line with anybody that we play
at this point. It's him. We have to
disrupt him and and then we can't let
the run game get going.
You know, these guys are going to
they're going to lean on you. They're
they're going to
they're going to use the run game cuz
it'll alleviate a ton of pressure and uh
>> [snorts]
>> if we let them open the floodgates, it's
going to be a long day for us. How do
you how do you feel just about playing
on Christmas? I mean you might be
working anyways, I guess a little bit,
but it's typically been a day that has
Listen, that's it's on the schedule. We
roll. It's what we're doing.
So we're going to be ready.
Uh that first game, the blitz obviously
got after the O line a little, but it
was a tough day in the backfield in
terms of protection. Just how do you
look at that? How do you adjust? Just
how do you have to weigh that? Yeah, I
mean that look, we look at all of that
and you know, we we know in totality we
have to be better and that's that's us
as coaches.
Um you know, we got to execute better.
Um
you know, we you know, I go back to the
game. We made so many mistakes um
and
all over the map, you know.
Um
and so we we just got to eliminate the
errors. But let's just eliminate the
errors. Look, our backs going to have to
protect. They know that. They're going
to and so is the O line and and so are
the tight ends at times. You're going to
have to they'll chip and nudge and
um you know, and then sometimes you got
to beat the rush with your receivers.
You got to play faster than the rush
comes. So
um and golf's got to roll. So
it it takes everybody.
Just just back to playing on on
Christmas. If you weren't playing, would
you be working like at night? How would
your how would your Christmas day be if
you were playing?
>> Man, I Dave, I hadn't even thought about
it.
I hadn't even thought about it. I mean I
think last year it was on an off day,
wasn't it or a
I think or was it not? Was it a
Wednesday? I don't know.
So I'm not sure. What I hadn't thought
anything about it really.
Can I ask you something just kind of
lighthearted about the holiday? Is there
a particular particular Christmas gift
that you ever received that
made kind of a a lasting memory on you
as a kid or an adult, whenever?
Uh
Well, I laughed cuz my my dad would
always get me underwear for
for Christmas. That was always the
running joke. It was just some tighty
whities.
So
Kids now? And actually mom got them, but
he always said they were from him. That
was his recommendation. A football or
Always makes me laugh.
But
No, that's not something I passed on to
my kids.
But
anyway, Christmas is a special time, you
know, I love Christmas and family and
friends and all that and uh
so we just need to win.
We need to win. From a play calling
perspective, what what do you kind of
have to be ready for going up against
Flores and and call plays and just kind
of being in in that environment?
Well, the first thing you got to be
ready ready for is everything and then
you need to be ready for everything
next.
And then maybe maybe after that it's
almost everything.
So um
you know, he keeps you on your toes. He
does a lot. He does a lot and uh
he's going to see if you got an answer
for it. Um
so it it's there again, it's going to
it'll take all of us and that includes
me. So he he does a ton. Always has and
they've evolved so much now, you know,
this is
this is he's been there a while and the
system is in and it's evolved now.
All everybody being together, all those
guys and
and it's pretty advanced now.
Do you put more on golf's plate from
that protection standpoint just cuz of
how complicated it is or is he ready to
handle you know, all the
I mean I would say if it is, yeah, it'll
be more on golf, but yet Kingsley knows
he knows
he knows what we need to do per this
week and what we're looking for and if
there needs to be alterations, you know,
golf will make those.
For you and some of your staff members
said before like at some point during a
rookie season, you stop being a rookie.
How do you say it? About 400 defensive
snaps now probably fits that that
definition. I'm just curious where
you've seen
you know, the most [snorts] growth from
him since he's progressed came in
kind of advanced where he came from
program wise, but
where is he in his development? Uh well,
I would say when
when you look at it
from start to finish, he has improved.
He's a better player than he started.
But he's like
um
really like all the rookies, there are
inconsistencies, you know, and the run
game is where he's really showed up.
But he has improved and I would say
uh really every week those
inconsistencies get less and less.
That's probably the best way to say it
and that's kind of the growth of a
rookie. So I like where he's going. Um
you're always going to have growing
pains.
You know, and he works at it. So he's
he's good and he's in a good rotation
with those guys. You know, he's been
playing quite a bit. We got Mack, we got
Lowe, Faze um Reader obviously, so
um he's part of that group.
It's all right.
>> [music]
[music]